A Guide to the James Branch Cabell Collection
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #5285
James Branch Cabell Collection 1915-1948
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
5285
ca. 30 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Purchase, 1956 Jan 30
Container List
- Letters
  - James Branch Cabell to McBride, Nast, & Co., 1915 Feb 20; ALS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to [A.L.S.] Woods [Wood], 1919 Feb 28; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to [A.L.S.] Wood, 1919 Mar 15; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Wood, 1921 Jan 21; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Wood, 1921 Jul 15; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Wood, 1921 Aug 5; ALS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Wood, 1921 Aug 31; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Wood, 1921 Sep 23; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Wood, 1921 Oct 14; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Wood, 1921 Oct 26; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Wood, 1921 Nov 28; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Wood, 1922 Jul 29; ALS, 1 p. (w/env)
  - James Branch Cabell to Wood, 1923 Dec 29; TLS, 1 p. (w/env)
  - James Branch Cabell to Wood, 1924 Dec 10; TLS, 1 p.
  - Mr. and Mrs. James Branch Cabell to Mrs. and Mrs. Wood, [1924 Dec 20]; Christmas card
  - James Branch Cabell to Burton [Rascoe], 1934 Jul 10; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Atlas Book Store, encl. TL, 1 p., Nov 15, Atlas Book Shop to James Branch Cabell, 1938 Nov 14; TLS, 1 p. (w/env)
  - James Branch Cabell to Robert Benaway Brown, 1941 Apr 20; TLS, 1 p. (w/env)
  - James Branch Cabell to [Robert Benaway] Brown, 1942 Jan 15; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to [Robert Benaway] Brown, 1945 Jun 4; TLS, 1 p. (w/env)
  - James Branch Cabell to [Robert Benaway] Brown, 1945 Jun 17; TLS, 1 p. (w/env)
  - James Branch Cabell to [Robert Benaway] Brown, 1945 Jun 29; TLS, 1 p. (w/env)
  - James Branch Cabell to [Robert Benaway] Brown, 1946 May 10; TLS, 1 p. (w/env)
  - James Branch Cabell to Watt Marchman, 1946 May 20; TLS, 1 p. (w/env)
  - James Branch Cabell to [Robert Benaway] Brown, 1947 Feb 11; TLS, 1 p. (w/env)
  - James Branch Cabell to [Robert Benaway] Brown, 1947 Feb 20; TLS, 1 p. (w/env)
  - James Branch Cabell to [Robert Benaway] Brown, [1947 Dec]; Christmas card(w/env)
  - Mr. and Mrs. James Branch Cabell to [Robert Benaway] Brown, [1948 Dec 16]; Christmas card(w/env)
  - James Branch Cabell to Wood, n.d.; TLS, 1 p.
  - Mr. and Mrs. James Branch Cabell to unknown, 2 Christmas cards